{"data":[{"question":"English is one of the most widely ___ international languages.","a":"using","b":"use","c":"to use","d":"used","answer":"4","explain":"\n- A participle is a verb form which can be used as an adjective to describe a noun \n+ When the present participle (-ing from) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) the performer of the activity named by the participle \n+ When the past participle (-ed, -en form) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) acted upon","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"___ language forms are different from ___ ones in many ways.","a":"Speaking, written","b":"Spoken, written","c":"Speak, write","d":"Spoken, writing","answer":"2","explain":"\n- A participle is a verb form which can be used as an adjective to describe a noun \n+ When the present participle (-ing from) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) the performer of the activity named by the participle \n+ When the past participle (-ed, -en form) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) acted upon","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"___ in 1886, the car was the oldest one in the race.","a":"It was built","b":"Built","c":"Having been built","d":"Being built","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Passive voice in relative clause, sometime we can ignore which\/that\/ who","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"___ many times, but he still didn't know how to do it well.","a":"Having been taught","b":"Being taught","c":"He had been taught","d":"Taught","answer":"3","explain":"\n- But + clause: can't stand independently. Therefore we need a main clause before or after","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Do you want to give a talk on that topic? \" ___ \"","a":"I prefer not","b":"I wouldn't prefer","c":"I prefer to not","d":"I prefer not to","answer":"4","explain":"\n- When reply to a question we can ignore the same Verb and only ignore that Verb \n+ I prefer not to= I prefer not to give","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Jasmine set out soon after dawn ___ home two hours later.","a":"to arrive","b":"arriving","c":"and arrived","d":"having arrived","answer":"3","explain":"\n- \"Arrived\" has same role as \"set\", the two verb describe the two independent action","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"It is rude ___ at a visitor.","a":"stared","b":"staring","c":"stare","d":"to stare","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Structure: it's + adj + to Verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"The lucky dog feels the time has come ___ around for a new job.","a":"to him to begin to look","b":"to him to begin looking","c":"for him beginning to look","d":"for him to begin looking","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Time\/ opportunity... has come for somebody to do something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"The problem now ___ at the meeting is very troublesome.","a":"to be discussed","b":"being discussed","c":"which is discussing","d":"discussed","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Passive voice in relative clause, sometime we can ignore which\/that\/ who","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"I'm sorry there's no knife or scissors for you ___.","a":"cutting","b":"to cut","c":"to cut it with","d":"to cut it","answer":"3","explain":"- There be something for somebody to do something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"}]}